yo what's going on everybody this is
going to be
on episode four right last episode was
nice um there was a lack of angles last
episode which i think they're going to
make up for in this one so
um and we're gonna see what kind of
scales we got this episode for so you
know we're gonna get this thing started
but before before we get this thing
started you know please help this
channel if not already i'm trying to get
to 16k subscribing sub will really help
out a lot i really appreciate it also i
do have a twitch channel which i'm back
on
on halloween the 31st of this month uh
starting around 7pm pst um my username
is right there and i do i have a patreon
where i post full anime reactions as
well as tons of other perks so do check
that out um my username for my patreon
right there and to link to all of those
going to be in the description below
what's up happy cybernet
let's get started
[Music]
oh [__] ohio
oh
well damn
we having a dirty dream okay
so i'll beat his eye
oh it's just cute
she's been having a bad dream uh she
didn't recollect it [__] man
that's worse dude like you just like
wake up and you're like you have this
feeling right but you can't remember
what the dream was dude it's so weird
it's so weird dog
oh chestnut pudding that sounds amazing
dog
yeah we all gotta get one
i'm not a pudding guy but like
the sounds of that just sounds crazy you
know i mean
must be nice to have all those calories
go straight to your boobs
hey
yo
oh
my god
that looks wild dawg
jesus christ man
yeah i love how she just doesn't flinch
dog jesus
what's going on here
oh this army
it added the three percent taxes
like wow
this goes pretty good
so that person must be a former worker
that maybe
[Music]
committed um seppuku um suicide or maybe
something i don't know but his neck had
holes in it it was long
bro bro oh gosh is so hot bro
look at her
every time dude
though hot okazan's in anime is just
like they're just goated man they're
just like on a different level than
everyone else you know what i'm saying
it's just
it's the milk effect
real scary stories okay
is there something intent or what's up
oh
i see you
i totally added it in
yeah yeah yeah you're right yeah of
course
exactly [__] the mads bro no cap
what what's going on
oh
yeah yeah okay
wait what's going on she got spooked out
from that
she's kind of thirsty i'm thirsty too
she's so dead
nah man
whoa that is a small ass homie
you okay dog
start running away
a tiny old man
yeah it's kind of cute watch it watch
turn back the corners are big
now i bet you that's gonna have a watch
watch watch
so why are you playing with ghosts doug
like like why why are you trying to play
with some tiny ass what's wrong with you
oh
what is that
oh what is that what it is what is that
bro you have a big schnozer
and you're tea bagging some dude man
like what's going
at on wait is it hopping in his mouth
that's home
slowly now slowly now don't make some
sudden movements we don't want that
oh hell nah
just snaggy oh slowly come on
what is that
could you smell it too
can't do this i know it's probably
smells nasty over there dog
huh
that crow broke or something like
so random ass code just just just
snagged that
500 okay
you know what dog
[__] it dog
perfect excuse to get the [__] out of
there
oh my god it's so cute man
my money got stolen
yup
give us that [__] back dog what's wrong
still playing around with me man
they were shopping shh
oh
little bros over here followed us
in a weird mood all the time
she got a boyfriend
ah so she started scott he started
scouting her out i see what's going on
this hair is crazy though she might be
important later on
yeah there's no way she has a boyfriend
though he's just
that's just a good cap honestly
oh
oh hell nah it's not like that bro
a creepy bastard
the word it's not that type of off-brand
anime come on bro you good
oh god again bro
yeah just slide it back in bro be out of
here
is it what you're looking at
okay dude why is the paranormal stuff
over the
like what
it makes no sense there's no
what
bro yeah you weren't even paying
attention to the type of book she put
she put she was like reading bro
ah nice water once again
we're out here dog
home sweet home you know what i'm saying
we're like kind of safe i guess
take it or leave it because this is the
best that we could get you know
oh sh
here it goes what do you mean
no way you're gonna go right in what
yo what is that
oh she's gonna jump down right now
don't flinch miss
like why are you just here bro like i
just don't get it like you know what i'm
saying like can you leave
privacy
is the best policy like i don't what's
wrong with you
oh she was imagining things
uh
oh
what does that hold me doing like taking
taking a bath or what
yeah man this is her comfy space man not
in the bathroom bro
bro what is you doing dog
big dog
i figured i'd join you okay really
good she doesn't have any hookies okay
she's so cute bro
he's hella scared
i wonder what happened to that ghost
that ghosts look very very skinny
um possibly some like otaku guy that
possibly died from um being
like not eating for a long period of
time possibly
i don't know
a wish today i won't see them oh
that's good cap
whoa dude
yeah we got some good angles this
episode man yes sir
what the hell
that's a big app
yo that's not a person dog that's like a
a dragon wolf like
what is that
what is that dog
that is hella disgusting bro
your boyfriend dump you okay
this is like the last of our worries dog
oh wait this is like a really bad
predicament for mikko bro
she's just trying to eat breakfast dog
yo why you just lick her food like that
bruh
this is probably like the worst
situation
there's no way this homie's leaving
i think this homie just came here for
her mom to be honest
she's not hungry nah nah she's probably
gonna be extremely hungry when she heads
out to school for sure
are we gonna try to like exercise to go
so like how's this even gonna work
oh what's going on with her
huh
wait
what
damn bro
holy [__] that [__] hurt that [__] hit
so fast
damn
my heart man
god damn
yo that [__] hit so fast bro
yo why why show her a [__] dad in in
with the regular animation bro why do
you all do that why did anime create
creators do that to us bro
i feel betrayed
i feel absolutely betrayed dude my heart
[__] hurts from that bro that [__]
actually hurts dog
oh my god
[__] that was rough
i was up for sure holy [__] almost
almost got me
100 photos all right here it comes
oh is that what she saw
i see
so that's why she flinched like that
ah
i love her face bro
the commercial though
oh oh
is this mr hansi
just like before
damn put straight on her neck bro
shh
i get it man that ghost is a fiend
uh
goes on
doesn't doesn't see what the hell is on
tv bro
what the hell dude
all right next episode i see them too
it's probably gonna we're probably gonna
talk to that chick with the uh with the
fire here but like you know um there's
that but um
obviously this episode was um it sucked
a lot for that last morning but
yeah overall and if you just put
everything together it's just like
it was uh
pretty
awesome i guess
yo guys it just hit me now
that the pudding wasn't for herself
it was literally just for her dad
literally just for it like she didn't
want to eat it because um i i think it
now when they were back in the
supermarket um con beanie there she was
talking about like how
how um hannah could stuff all those
calories in her and it goes straight to
her breasts
but like i was like thinking that was a
little bit hypocritical but like at the
end
she it was just for her dad pudding so
that [__] even harder bro
[__]
damn it man
uh
it was actually i was i was starting to
get like it was a little tilting see
that see that um that thing right there
in the morning um but then again after
that like brought everything together
with their dad bro that [__] hit
that should actually hit but um yeah man
this episode was really wholesome at the
end it was very sad at the end actually
it was very sad um we also had that
shower scene which was
i liked it a lot yes yeah
um
yeah it feels like the worst the days
are getting worse and worse to be honest
i don't know why um but yeah we'll have
to wait and see what happens in the next
episode um i'm um yeah i mean i'm
curious hope y'all are excited for that
one as well you know um as always do let
me know in the comment section below if
i miss anything or misinterpret or
something is up so do put it out to me
but uh would that be said for now
i'm out of here
my socials are going to be right here
those links are going to be in the
description below as well i highly
recommend people join discord if you
have not joined this score yet that
would be twitter because about those
i'll let people know whenever we go live
on twitch right uh whenever it goes up
on youtube or just any community like
stuff that goes on that i want to let
y'all know about let y'all know on there
as well
if you like this video like and
subscribe subscribe let's get there
especially for you watch it's gonna be
up there the most recent video that
posted my channel is gonna be right down
there so
happy ceremony thanks for watching i'll
see everyone in the next episode
peace